<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="eclipse-loc-plugin-feature"
      label="Eclipse GenAI LOC Tracker"
      version="1.0.0.202605251227"
      provider-name="CTS">

   <description>
      Eclipse GenAI LOC Tracker

Tracks Lines of Code (LOC) generated with GitHub Copilot and other GenAI
assistants inside the Eclipse IDE. Events captured by this plugin are
posted to the Spring Boot LOC service that is also used by the companion
IntelliJ plugin, providing a unified view of AI-assisted productivity
across both IDEs.

Features:
  - Captures inline accept / tab-completion events from Copilot
  - Aggregates LOC counts per file, project, and session
  - Posts metrics asynchronously to the configured LOC service endpoint
  - Honors workspace-level enable/disable preferences
   </description>

   <copyright url="https://www.cognizant.com">
      Copyright (c) 2026 Cognizant Technology Solutions (CTS).
All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">
      Eclipse GenAI LOC Tracker
Copyright (c) 2026 Cognizant Technology Solutions. All rights reserved.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this software except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

USAGE
-----
This plugin instruments the Eclipse IDE to track AI-assisted lines of
code (LOC) generated by GitHub Copilot and other GenAI tooling. Telemetry
is collected per Cognizant's internal data-handling policies and is
intended for productivity analytics only. No source code content is
transmitted off the developer's machine; only aggregate LOC counts and
event metadata are sent to the configured Spring Boot LOC service.

DATA COLLECTED
--------------
  - Number of AI-suggested lines accepted / rejected
  - File extension and project name (no file contents)
  - Timestamp and IDE session identifier
  - User identifier (corporate email / SSO id) for attribution

DISCLAIMER
----------
Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
implied. See the License for the specific language governing
permissions and limitations under the License.

By clicking "I accept the terms of the license agreement" you
acknowledge that usage metrics will be collected by this plugin in
accordance with Cognizant's internal data-handling policies.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="com.cts.plugin.eclipse.loc"
         version="1.0.0.202605251227"/>

</feature>
